<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<books>
    <book>
        <isbn>031242194X</isbn>
        <title>Someone to Run With</title>
        <author>David Grossman</author>
        <edition>Italian</edition>
        <publisher>Mondadori</publisher>
        <format>Paperback</format>
        <description>The story of a lost dog, and the discovery of first love on the streets of Jerusalem are portrayed here with a gritty realism that is as fresh as it is compelling.

When awkward and painfully shy sixteen-year-old Assaf is asked to find the owner of a stray yellow lab, he begins a quest that will bring him into contact with street kids and criminals, and a talented young singer, Tamar, engaged on her own mission: to rescue a teenage drug addict.

A runaway bestseller in Israel, in the words of the Christian Science Monitor: &quot;It's time for Americans to fall in love with Someone to Run With.&quot;</description>
        <publishing_date>01/02/2017</publishing_date>
        <rating>3.625</rating>
        <genres/>
        <ratings>
            <rating_u>3</rating_u>
            <rating_u>5</rating_u>
            <rating_u>5</rating_u>
            <rating_u>1</rating_u>
            <rating_u>4</rating_u>
            <rating_u>4</rating_u>
            <rating_u>5</rating_u>
            <rating_u>5</rating_u>
            <rating_u>2</rating_u>
            <rating_u>2</rating_u>
            <rating_u>4</rating_u>
            <rating_u>4</rating_u>
            <rating_u>4</rating_u>
            <rating_u>4</rating_u>
            <rating_u>3</rating_u>
            <rating_u>3</rating_u>
        </ratings>
        <quotes/>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <user>fedebrichi</user>
                <review_content>Nope</review_content>
            </review>
            <review>
                <user>gesu</user>
                <review_content>I can walk on wateeeer
</review_content>
            </review>
            <review>
                <user>pirlott</user>
                <review_content>Faasdasd</review_content>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </book>
    <book>
        <isbn>0374528373</isbn>
        <title>The Brothers Karamazov</title>
        <author>Fyodor Dostoyevsky</author>
        <edition>English</edition>
        <publisher>Farrar Straus and Giroux</publisher>
        <format>Paperback</format>
        <description>The Brothers Karamazov is a passionate philosophical novel set in 19th century Russia, that enters deeply into the ethical debates of God, free will, and morality. It is a spiritual drama of moral struggles concerning faith, doubt, and reason, set against a modernizing Russia.</description>
        <publishing_date>23/07/1993</publishing_date>
        <rating>3</rating>
        <genres/>
        <ratings>
            <rating_u>3</rating_u>
            <rating_u>3</rating_u>
            <rating_u>2</rating_u>
            <rating_u>2</rating_u>
            <rating_u>4</rating_u>
            <rating_u>4</rating_u>
        </ratings>
        <quotes/>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <user>fedebrichi</user>
                <review_content>Il mio nuovo taglio di capelli lo odiano tutti. :(</review_content>
            </review>
            <review>
                <user>gesu</user>
                <review_content>I can walk on wateeeer
</review_content>
            </review>
            <review>
                <user>pirlott</user>
                <review_content>Brilliant!</review_content>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </book>
    <book>
        <isbn>343432423432</isbn>
        <title>Brisingr (The Inheritance Cycle #5)</title>
        <author> Christopher Paolini</author>
        <edition>English</edition>
        <publisher>Alfred A. Knopf</publisher>
        <format>Paperback</format>
        <description>Oaths sworn... loyalties tested... forces collide. It's been only months since Eragon first uttered &quot;brisingr&quot;, an ancient language term for fire. Since then, he's not only learned to create magic with words — he's been challenged to his very core. Following the colossal battle against the Empires warriors on the Burning Plains, Eragon and his dragon, Saphira, have narrowly escaped with their lives. Still, there is more adventure at hand for the Rider and his dragon, as Eragon finds himself bound by a tangle of promises he may not be able to keep. First is Eragon's oath to his cousin, Roran: to help rescue Roran's beloved from King Galbatorix's clutches. But Eragon owes his loyalty to others, too. The Varden are in desperate need of his talents and strength — as are the elves and dwarves. When unrest claims the rebels and danger strikes from every corner, Eragon must make choices — choices that will take him across the Empire and beyond, choices that may lead to unimagined sacrifice. Eragon is the greatest hope to rid the land of tyranny. Can this once simple farm boy unite the rebel forces and defeat the king? </description>
        <publishing_date>20/09/2008</publishing_date>
        <rating>2</rating>
        <genres/>
        <ratings>
            <rating_u>2</rating_u>
            <rating_u>2</rating_u>
        </ratings>
        <quotes/>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <user>pirlott</user>
                <review_content>So, I was a little disappointed with this third installment of Paolini's Inheritance &quot;Cycle&quot; now - since he changed the game and made this a 4 book series instead of 3, as it was originally intended. The story was good and what I have come to expect from this series. But honestly, it did not have to be 748 pages long. I understand the author's desire to flesh out his characters, but the way that he kept going back and forth between the different characters I found annoying. The descriptions of the fights did not have to be as gory or detailed as he made them, nor as long as he made them. I had several guesses going throughout the book about how the plot would unfold and I ended up getting it right - though the character I thought was being set up to die did not. There are also points of the book where I can clearly see familiar plot points that I have seen in other books or series, like Star Wars or LOTR. I also found Paolini's waxing on religion and philosophy through his main character annoying - it's as if he is trying to make this series more poignant than it is should be - because after all, it is just a good fantasy tale at its core and I feel like he should just stick to those roots. I will be interested to see how Paolini wraps this complex story up. He has woven a lot of moving parts together and they are all pretty complex and I wonder how the climatic battle between good and evil will finally play out. I just hope I won't have to wade through another 800 some pages to get to the end.</review_content>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </book>
    <book>
        <isbn>432354435</isbn>
        <title>534543</title>
        <author>3455343</author>
        <edition>43453</edition>
        <publisher>5444</publisher>
        <format>5344</format>
        <description>54345354</description>
        <publishing_date>01/01/1753</publishing_date>
        <rating>3</rating>
        <genres/>
        <ratings>
            <rating_u>3</rating_u>
            <rating_u>3</rating_u>
        </ratings>
        <quotes/>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <user>pirlott</user>
                <review_content>dfdfdd</review_content>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </book>
</books>
